

Harun Erkam BALI
Telephone Number: +90 537 551 28 75
E-Mail: harunerkam0@gmail.com

Kaggle: https://www.kaggle.com/harunerkambali Github: https://github.com/erkamspyjamas

#### Personal Information

Place of Birth: Istanbul / Ümraniye

Date of Birth: 2001

#### Education

**2019 - 2023** 

Management Information Systems – Necmettin Erbakan Universty

#### About Me

My love for computers, which started at a young age, has been the basis of my interest in technology until today. I love to research and learn new technologies. Artificial intelligence topics intrigue me. I'm into image processing and machine learning with Python. I can code whatever I want.

## **Experience**

Autodidactic Technologies (2022-2023)

R&D Engineer (Intern)

I professionally learned how to develop artificial intelligence and the approach to be followed with Reinforcement Learning.

Neurosound (2023-Present)

Software Dev. & IT Specialist

### <u>Language</u>

English: I am good in reading comprehension and intermediate in writing and speaking.

## Knowledge

- I can describe myself as a Junior Python Developer.
- I can do visual programming with Java.
- I have enough knowledge to make a game with C# using Unity.
- I can make a simple mobile program with Java in Android Studio.
- I can create static sites with HTML, CSS, Javascript, and I can create simple database-related sites with PHP.
- I can analyse data, visualize and modeling.

# <u>Hobbies</u>

Listen to music, Playing video games, Research, Taking photographs, Watching sports, Take a trip.